[{"answer": "You can Google it.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "How bad was it?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "You enjoy the status of television icon?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "You're that guy.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Oh, well, you know?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, some of my --", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "How does it go down with all your famous friends?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "It's pretty lonely, but you know they seem to tolerate me somehow, because I can at least state myself eloquently and without actually kind of assuming what they -- the veneer of what they assume is what a Republican is, as some kind of nasty, strange villain that, you know, should be vilified and hated.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Is it lonely out there?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "So, you did do the hard yards of theatrical trainings, didn't you, to be a serious actor?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Did you ever imagine at that stage, at Juilliard, you're looking around, all these talented people presumably -- did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams or maybe nightmares the level of fame that you would one day get through acting?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "And in the back of your mind all you're thinking of is this could tank, and then what?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Yes, we were together in school.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "You trained with him at the Julliard, didn't he?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "But is part of that because you've managed to deal with so many of the demons that you carry?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, there were -- there were several along the way, where I just -- you know, I'd sit there and say, I've got to stop.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What was the -- what was the wake up moment for you?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, actually, I did go to Betty Ford, and that helped.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "How did you manage to stop in the end?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "I have a drink sometimes, yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "You can drink in moderation?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "It's interesting.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "How did it feel to you?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "That was another night.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Did she fire a gun at you?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Yes, no, this is the -- this is what --", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "You married her after she shot at you?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "I tell you, it was absurdly across -- a shot across the bow.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Wasn't that a warning sign, get off it?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "So that fell apart pretty quickly.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "A woman shoots at me, I'm thinking twice about the marriage, you know?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, I have to -- I mean, I have to tell you, my -- \"The Real Housewives\" was my parting gift to her.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "This must have been like hell, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Well, they're not good.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "But -- I mean, how are things?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "We have no contact, no.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Do you have any kind of dialogue with her?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Oh, it's great.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "How is your relationship with them?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, they're trying to -- they're doing their best to actually kind of make that difficult for me right now.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "You get plenty of access?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "No, I think she married me because I was Frasier.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Do you think she married you because you were Kelsey Grammer, TV icon?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I think it was Frasier.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I haven't been keeping track of everything, so there might be something that would surprise me.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "What's been worst thing, the most hurtful thing she said about you?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "She once said that I didn't want my daughter.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "What's the most unfair labeling?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Yes, well, it would, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "From Los Angeles.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "To England from New York?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "From Los Angeles?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Because Kayte is a very beautiful young lady, as we can see here.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Well, you know what?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Oh, I think she knew who I was, but she didn't know who I am.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Did she know who you were?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "She believes in love.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What is it about her you think that enabled her to deal with all this?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "It's been -- it was a presumptive joining (ph) of the work every day.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Are you really enjoying it?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "I love him.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Do you like him or not?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Isn't that you, in the end?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "RAMMER: Yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Do you feel for the first you've gone back to the joy of life you had as a young boy?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Ma, can I go?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Mom?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I feel great, actually.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "How are you feeling?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "I feel like -- across the years, it's been, like, mixed emotions.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "And did your mom always have this inkling you had what it took?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Do you feel you missed out on anything?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Stupid things like passing notes in school and having a locker and riding the bus, I mean, really stupid things.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "What do you feel that you missed on?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "It can be lonely, can't it?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "If your little boy gets to about 8 or 9...", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "And I think I was good at separating that and being, like, OK, well, they get this, but I get this, you know?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "Oh, it's so hard.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "... I want to be star, how can you stop it?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "From when I started to now, the industry is so different.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Why would you be so concerned?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "What is the least perfect thing about you?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "For you, the halo is, like, clasped on your head.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "You couldn't find anything?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Oh, this is a long time ago.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "What did you call Faye Dunaway?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "You can Google it.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "How bad was it?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "I'll let you know.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "Do you believe in love at first sight?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "Maybe you were looking, but you weren't really seeing.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "How could I have seen you before and not know who you are now?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 765, "question": "I mean, you've made a lot of money, haven't you?", "qSentId": 764}, {"answer": "I have done quite well.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "And said to her -- (INAUDIBLE) remind what you say to her?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "Yes, I love that!", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Do you like that?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "Well, she came back and said, you know, Oh, I never made that comment, and blah, blah, blah.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 797, "question": "Did it keep her quiet?", "qSentId": 796}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Well, I'm all for feuds.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "I mean, why would she say that to me?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "Quite a few.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Now, how many terrible frogs did you have to kiss before you got to him?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Oh, him by far.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "Who has the worst list, do you think?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "I don't think even hers is bigger than that.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "Didn't you have Kim Kardashian on the show?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 849, "question": "Is that what he gave you as an engagement ring?", "qSentId": 848}, {"answer": "Yes, I have.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111022pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "Did you actually write this?", "qSentId": 870}]